Destroyed the game stage to the hall
Hello, everyone. I'm Yuri Kitagawa, from Nogizaka 46.
I'm Sakura Kawasaki. Pleased to meet you.
Today we'd like to do the arena only.
Let's do our best. Let's do our best.
I'd be happy if you could study or work with me while watching this.
I'd like to do it.
Today, we're going to concentrate for 20 minutes and then take a 5 minute break, and I hope we can repeat this 3 times.
Let's concentrate and work hard together.
By the way, what are you working on today?
I have a lot of reports that are due for mid-term exams.
I'm hoping to get as far as I can with one of them.
What year are you in? I'm in my second year.
Sophomore. Yeah, there are a lot of reports.
There are a lot of them, so I'd like to finish at least one of them.
What are you working on, Yuri?
Yuri, you have one report and one...
Yuri, you have to write one report and one review of a project you've been working on.
I'm a professor, so I'll do my best to finish them in this time.
Let's be like that.
Yuri, four of these.
I drink a lot when I'm studying.
I don't know if my body temperature rises when I'm concentrating, but...
I drink to cool myself down.
I drink water, black tea, and my favorite black tea.
There are about four kinds of smoothies.
You can see this too!
We also have two kinds of tapioca.
If I get sleepy, I have black tea, and if I want to lower my body temperature, I have water.
You use them differently.
You open them all and take a sip at a time, and you can't finish studying until you've drunk them all.
I drank a lot of tapioca while studying in high school.
I would sneak out of school after school to buy tapioca and hide it in my bag.
I would go back to school and study.
Now, I'd like to start the 20-minute segment.
Is everyone ready for the 20 minutes?
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm fine.
So let's concentrate for 20 minutes.
Here we go!
적으로
Shit.
Nozzle
Ronald
self
shit
chocolate
helper
vor
empowerment
chichi
sbo
vsu
in
hora
Sano
Mo
Purple
grass
Japanese cypress (Chamaecyparis obtusa)
Japanese pepper (Zanthoxylum piperitum)
collection
crime
of
by H.
H.
Hm
mmm
vap
voodoo
hmm
vap
den
conviction
voodoo
Conviction voodoo
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
conviction
Conviction voodoo
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
meme
MEME
mmm
Hm
extract
mmm
conviction
Conviction voodoo
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
M
me
,,
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
mmm
Hm...
[Please subscribe to our channel.
Mmm
Nm
Hm
mmm
Thank you for watching!
Hm
me
m
N
Hmm?
mmm
Hm
me
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Thank you for watching!
mmm
Please subscribe to our channel!
Time has passed.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
See you again.
Bye.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Mmm
Mmm.
Mmm...
Hm?
Hm
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
by H.
That didn't take long.
How far along are you?
But, you know, the one to date is pretty...
A light report?
It's more like a short report.
I just finished it and was rereading it.
That's great.
I saw the movie a long time ago.
Oh, I see.
I was doing a lot of research to jog my memory.
Oh, that's great!
I couldn't picture the details.
It's hard to get that far, that's for sure.
I have some snacks.
I could bring you some snacks.
I'd like to go.
Let's go.
I brought snacks.
Yay!
Do you usually eat sweets? When I'm studying.
I like to sample sweets.
Oh, I see.
I eat a lot of sweets.
Do you eat sweets often?
I like sweets.
Oh, I see.
I like them so much that I even have them for breakfast.
I like this a lot, too.
Oh, I see.
That's nice.
How about you, Yuri?
Thank you. For always listening.
I like gummy bears.
They're so cute.
Are these gummies?
Yeah, these are Barfurds.
I thought they were marshmallows.
They are.
Gummies like that.
It's like a cross between a gummy bear and a marshmallow.
I love them. I love them.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Tea.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Lately...
Psychology?
I've been studying a little bit of...
I've always been interested in it.
I've never really studied it before.
Crowd mentality.
Oh...
Discrimination based on stereotypes.
Psychology is very close to me.
Ah...
That's why it's so much fun.
It's a lot more fun than I thought it would be.
I'm in my fourth year.
Yeah, yeah.
I took a class my junior year.
I took a class called Psychology of Perception and Information.
Mm-hmm.
What's that sound like?
Mm-hm-hm.
and psychology.
Heh.
I've been studying.
So it's like...
I feel like I'm in a distant place.
I was shown an image of my back.
Oh, wow.
And you're being touched.
And I feel like I'm being touched too.
I feel like I'm leaving Yutan.
Heh.
Sounds interesting.
Interesting.
It's like that.
Psychology is interesting, isn't it?
Hey.
Well, I'd like to start another 20 minutes.
I'll push.
Okay, I'll go.
Okay.
All right, let's go.All right, let's get started!
Wait a minute.
Good night.
Today we have a name właściwie.
This beautiful chicken
In a different rice cooker
Avenge the great shit chicken
I was enjoying
Saங and
fight
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
hee hee hee
spur goza
Dizzy
mmm
Mmm.
Hm
mmm
mn
'n' (unit of volume, approx. 1.8 ml)
Nm
mn
mnn
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
Hm
Pooh!
me
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Hm
mmm
Arrived
Chocolate is squeezed.
The strip is a cutter.
The cutter is very fine.
Then, one layer of chocolate...
We take a lot of chocolate
Salt to taste kaufen
Finished processing
Attention!
Hm.
mmm
Hm?
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
a lot
'n' (used to indicate agreement with something said or done)
'n' (used to indicate a negative verb, e.g. 'n', 'n')
'n' (used to indicate a negative conditional)
nn
hmm
mmm
Hm
[ED]
Oh, my God, it's so big.
40 minutes have passed?
Yes, indeed.
It went by pretty fast, didn't it? 40 minutes.
It's only been like 15 minutes.
Mm-hmm.
Do you listen to music while you study?
I do.
Listen?
I listen to something like a music box.
Me too.
Like the sound of waves.
Like music.
I can't listen to music with lyrics.
Or I listen to the same album over and over.
I listen to it over and over.
My ear gets used to it.
I'm like, "Okay, I'm going to play the bass on this song.
And I'm like...
It's like a scene reflex.
I used to listen to the same song over and over again.
That's true, me too.
I'm the type of person that once I like a song
I'll listen to it forever.
Oh, really?
It's good, isn't it?
Till I get tired of it.
I can see why.
I listen to the same songs all the time.
I don't know.
I have my theme song every month.
But I get it.
I get it.
I feel like I understand.
I wonder if it's similar to that feeling.
Yes, we are similar.
There are a lot of similarities.
I feel like we have a lot in common.
I miss you.
It's the only thing I miss.
I don't know...
I felt at home just by being with you.
I'm so happy
I'll miss you so much.
But...
I'm really looking forward to your future.
I'm so excited!
The morning before
when we made the announcement
Sakira-san cried for me.
I cried so hard.
And she called me.
I don't know...
I don't know what to say.It's like this.
I'm so happy to have such a cute junior
I'm so happy.
And we have fun together.
So I'm really happy.
Thank you.
No, no, no. I'm glad to hear it.
I'm glad you call me Yuri-chan.
Since the beginning.
I'm the only one who calls you that.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Shall we do it?
I hope you're all ready for this.
What are you doing, by the way?
Someone.
I'm curious.
Did you hear that?
Yeah, I did.
She said something about an assignment or work.
You heard me.
Okay, last one.
Let's go for the last spurt.
Let's do our best.
Okay, then.
I'll push.
I wonder if this is it.
I don't know if I can finish in the next 20 minutes.
I'd love to talk.
I'm gonna push.
Let's do 20 minutes.
Then we'll talk.
I'll go.
Okay, let's start setting up.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mm.
Mnh-mnh.
Mmm
mmm
Hm...
[Please subscribe to our channel.
Mmm
Nm
Hm
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Mmm
Nm
Hm
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Thank you for watching!
mmm
.......
for watching this short video, really thanks so much for watching this short video of mine.
For watching this short video, your 지 really thanks so much for watching this short video of mine.
Hmm...
hmm
mmm
I don't know...
I am living in the day on the other direction and watching the flight of the plane paraphernalia on the graph or the plane's how many consciousness shaking in the ear and not hear the big shuolve and not hear
I can't hear it.
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Hmm?
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Hm
mmm
Mnh-mnh.
Good night.
Oh, man, I just want to do the test.
Yeah, okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is it done?
Yeah, I'm done.
Wow, that was fast.
That went really fast, an hour. Yeah, it flew by. How did it go?
I wrote down both hands, so now I just need to connect them at home.
That's the hardest part. Did it go fast?
I'll try it.
I'm sorry, but when I'm working alone, I have to take breaks all the time.
I'd be happy if you could watch this video and focus on it with me.
I think it's good to break it up into 20-minute segments like this.
Even during the break time.
Once you start looking at your cell phone, you can't go back to studying.
I can't go back to study.
I've had enough of it.
But you can do it by having a time table like this.
I didn't introduce this once.
I feel like everyone wants to hear about your study methods.
Please introduce them to us!
Yuri-chan's study method
I'd like to share a little bit about my study method.
I use a lot of colors.
Instead of notebooks, I just write it down and I remember it.
Purple is for settings, blue is for grammar, and so on.
Like, "Just carry this one book with you and you'll be done.
So you used your textbook as a notebook?
I didn't take notes in math either.I didn't even take notes in math.
I just stared at the blackboard like this.
I was just trying to understand what was being solved.
I didn't want to go back and read my notes anyway.
I just wrote down what I didn't understand.
I think that's a very unique way to study.
In social studies, I took a lot of notes on everything the teacher said.
I don't know why he did that.
so that I don't lose track of it.
It's written in a way that you can understand the story.
So if I don't understand something, I have a note of what happened.
And then I can look it up later.
And I probably have a good ear.
I have a good ear, so I'm better at learning by listening than reading.
That's the type of person I am.
That's the type.
I can record myself explaining something and listen to it while I'm on the road.
Or I can make an audio word file on my computer and have it read out loud.
and have it read aloud to me.
It's great to hear that.
I feel like it's really helpful.
Thank you so much for listening.
How did it go? I did it today.
It went really fast.
But I was really, really focused.
I got a lot done.
I hope you all got a lot out of it.
Thank you for watching!
I would be happy if we could study and work together as many times as possible.
I would be happy if we could study and work together again and again.
I hope we can study and work together again and again.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a rating!
Seino bye-bye!